extraconversion.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy of ExtraConversion.com

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by ExtraConversion.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, ExtraConversion.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

ExtraConversion.com does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ExtraConversion.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to ExtraConversion.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google AdSense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on ExtraConversion.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.

Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

ExtraConversion.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

**Visitor Name and Email address**

We are not requiring visitor to provide any personal information such as name and Email address to us for visiting ExtraConversion.com

Visitors may provide their first name and email address to ExtraConversion.com. And the reason we collect the first name is we want to make more friendly when sending or replying email to the user.

When they subscribe to get free newsletter from ExtraConversion.com. We use this information for sending free newsletter to the users that subscribe to our database.

When they ask questions or provide comments to us. We use this information for replying back the question and comment that have been send to us. We also may also post name (but not Email address) with good comment or question on the website.

**The Change of This Privacy Policy**

Since we continued improvement our website and quality and adding new features, we may need to make some change or add some new policy when we necessary. We may not inform to the visitor about change; but we may publish about the change on a specific date later.

**Contacting ExtraConversion.com**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact us using the contact form.
